Chandler Tan

Aspiring Salesforce Developer

(219) 381-9256 tanchandler4@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://chandlert32.github.io/

Trailblazer Profile:

https://trailblazer.me/id/ctan4

Currently I am enrolled in the Salesforce Pathfinder Developer program with the goal of obtaining the Platform Developer I certification at the conclusion of the program in June 2020. I am also a recent graduate of Eleven Fifty Academy's Software Development program in which I learned the necessary skills to become a full-stack developer. I have experience with the languages of HTML, CSS, and C#. Furthermore, I implement these languages in many of my applications. Prior to Pathfinder and the Eleven Fifty program, I was majoring in Kinesiology and Exercise Science at Indiana State University. As of late, I have grown a passion for building software. I am motivated and committed to continuing my learning to become a Salesforce Developer.

EDUCATION

Salesforce Pathfinder Program, Developer Track

March 2020 - June 2020

40+ badges, 37,500+ points, 3 trails (Mountaineer Rank)

Learned the technical and business skills necessary to pursue a career in the Salesforce ecosystem. Technical skills including experience with lightning web components, fundamentals of the Salesforce platform, as well as testing and debugging using Apex language.

Eleven Fifty Academy, Fishers, IN — *Software Development*

Jan 2020 - April 2020

Gave me the tools to become an efficient software developer. Learned the object oriented fundamentals of C#. Gained experience with making Console, Web, and MVC applications. Gave me the confidence to make applications by myself, as well as in a team.

Indiana State University, Terre Haute, IN — *Studied Kinesiology and Exercise Science*

2015 - 2019

Activites: Men's soccer, intramural basketball

Merrillville High School, Merrillville, IN − Core 40

SKILLS

C# / HTML / CSS

Github

ASP.NET Web API

.NET Framework

MVC Application

Azure

Salesforce Fundamentals

Developer Tools

Apex

Lightning Web Components

Full-Stack experience

And more...

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Teamwork

Dependable

Curious

Patience

Punctual

And more...

PROJECTS - (also available on my github portfolio link...)

BlueBox — ASP.NET MVC, completed alone

Game and Movie Rental Service that utilizes .NET Framework MVC 5 Web Application using n-tier architecture. Tiers including data, models, services, and Web MVC. Allows users to rate a game/movie and rent. Implements user roles, full CRUD on multiple tables. Worked with razor syntax. Deployed to Azure.

Basic Db — database Web API, completed w/team of 4

.NET Framework API Web Application using n-tier architecture. Fictional character database that connects a character with their item (wand, sword, cloak, etc...) and type of media (movie, book, magazine, etc...). Includes custom data tables, and utilizes foreign key relationships between tables.

Hangman — console application, completed w/team of 2

Console app based around the fun game of 'Hangman'. Incorporated pair-programming.

Web Store Front — HTML & CSS homepage, completed alone

'Pizza Planet' home webpage using HTML and CSS.

CSS Creature — CSS, completed alone

Created a creature on codepen using only CSS.

EXPERIENCE

Eleven Fifty Academy— .NET Development Student

2020

Although I was just a student here, I feel like I learned the necessary skills to become a full-stack developer. Learned many skills ranging from building storefront websites to more complex applications such as an MVC application.

Indianapolis Comic Con — *Box Office Staff*

2017 - 2018

Worked at the 2017 and 2018 Indy Comic Con. Assisted customers in getting their ticket and letting them know where everything was at. Helped my bosses in moving cash boxes.

JC Penny — Retail Associate

2016 - 2018

Worked as a cashier as well as on the sales floor. Strived for accuracy when it came to getting work done. Assisted my boss and my peers by arranging the store and making sure everyone was doing their job correctly.

Toys R Us — Retail Associate

2016

Worked as a cashier as well as on the sales floor. Assisted customers with their needs. Made sure ailes were cleaned and aligned properly.

Certifications

Salesforce Platform Developer I — *estimated June* 2020

Red Badge (3/3 Eleven Fifty Academy) — April 2020

Earners of .NET Red Badge take all the skills they have learned in the previous badges and work individually to create a full stack web application with .NET framework MVC and Razor. Earners work solo to plan sprints.

Credentials:

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/9e3065fa-7d3f-4183-b9c2-bde631 dfc7ca/public_url

Blue Badge (2/3 Eleven Fifty Academy) — March 2020

Earners of .NET Blue Badge learn the basics of ASP.NET layered Web API development, SDLC (without maintenance), collaboration, applied problem solving, and debugging skills. Earners work in groups to plan sprints, execute daily stand ups, manage Git, intro to SOLID, and resolve issues with group dynamics.

Credentials:

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/535ea75a-d853-435a-87be-45118 3fbae02/public_url

Gold Badge (1/3 Eleven Fifty Academy)— February 2020

Earners of .NET Gold Badge learn fundamentals of C#, CSS, and HTML. They also learn developer tools, such as Visual Studio, Github, and Git. Earners show ability to meet deadlines and complete a series of business challenges covering C# and Object Oriented Programming fundamentals.

Credentials:

https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/e03e9cb2-fe02-43f5-b776-742ee 63ae796/public url